Topic - Javascript

Why language?

example vlc stored in ssd also it is open source - double click goes to ram in temrs of 01010, relate with vlc example
zoom, vlc, whatsapp, notepad - written in language (c,c++,js,rust) - compiler (complier complies to 010) - 01010 - ram, ssd

- languages are used to write applications
- developers write high level code in these languages
- every language has a compiler which converts the developer code into 01

interpreter vs compiler

Strict vs dynamic languages
Single threaded nature of JS
Simple primitives in JS (number, strings, booleans)
Complex primitives in JS (arrays, objects)
Functions in Javascript
Practise problem solving
Callback functions, Event loop, callback queue, Asynchronous programming
Callback hell and Promises