Topic - Javascript

Why language?

example vlc stored in ssd also it is open source - double click goes to ram in temrs of 01010, relate with vlc example
zoom, vlc, whatsapp, notepad - written in language (c,c++,js,rust) - compiler (complier complies to 010) - 01010 - ram, ssd

- languages are used to write applications
- developers write high level code in these languages
- every language has a compiler which converts the developer code into 01

